Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1910
  - Brown, Marion M. (Box 30)
  - Brown, Mary P. (Box 30)
  - Brown, Ruth L. (Box 30)
  - Bruce, Helen M. (Box 30)
  - Carnegie, Elza K. (Box 30)
  - Carpenter, Helen S. (Box 30)
  - Castle, Evelyn L. (Box 30)
  - Cates, Nell (Box 30)
  - Chichester, Charlotte B. (Box 30)
  - Clark, Alice (Box 30)
  - Clark, Dorothy S. (Box 30)
  - Cleveland, Marguerite C. (Box 30)
  - Collins, Margaret A. (Box 30)
  - Conover, Margaret B. (Box 30)
  - Creason, Katie M. (Box 30)
  - Cummins, Caroline S. (Box 30)
  - Cunningham, Florence (Box 30)
  - Cunningham, Mary P. (Box 30)
  - Damon, Gladys L. (Box 30)
  - Darwin, Mary (Box 30)
  - Davidson, Ethel M. (Box 30)
  - Dawson, Florence C. (Box 30)
  - Denton, Bessie Scott (Box 30)
  - Dickerman, Berenice (Box 30)
  - Dike, Alice M. (Box 30)
  - Downs, Lois M. (Box 30)
  - Drake, Quaesita C. (Box 30)
  - DuBois, Evelyn Spencer (Box 30)
  - Duke, Elizabeth (Box 30)
  - Dwight, Helen C. (Box 30)
  - Ebel, Anna B. (Box 30)
  - Edgar, Natalie (Box 30)
  - Elder, Vera (Box 30)
  - Ellis, Prudence H. (Box 30)
  - English, Stephanie K. (Box 30)
  - Erlich, Ruth J. (Box 30)
  - Ernst, Constance Q. (Box 30)
  - Erwin, Esther (Box 30)
  - Farmer, Alice H. (Box 30)
  - Fernald, Ruth (Box 30)
  - Fifield, Ruth A. (Box 30)
  - Fisher, Josephine Scott (Box 30)
  - Fleming, Martha E. (Box 30)
  - Fletcher, Margaret G. (Box 30)
  - Forbes, Cornelia B. (Box 30)
  - Gager, Bertha B. (Box 30)
  - Gailor, Charlotte (Box 30)
  - Gannett, Charlotte K. (Box 30)
  - Gardner, Hazel (Box 30)
  - Garland, Alice (Box 30)
  - Geddis, Bessie B. (Box 30)
  - Gibson, Clara (Box 30)
  - Gilbert, Sarah N. (Box 30)
  - Glass, Elsabeth L. (Box 30)
  - Godard, Guenn P. (Box 30)
  - Gonzalez, Juanita (Box 30)
  - Gordon, Cornelia (Box 30)
  - Gordon, Jessie (Box 30)
  - Gray, Zoe (Box 30)
  - Gregory, Allene (Box 30)
  - Grosche, Alene S. (Box 30)
  - Haines, Florence R. (Box 30)
  - Hamilton, Gabriella R. (Box 30)
  - Hanchette, Mary Estelle (Box 30)
  - Hand, Charlotte S. (Box 30)
  - Hanley, Harriet E. (Box 30)
  - Harbison, Lucy A. (Box 30)
  - Harding, Ruth E. (Box 30)
  - Hart, Edith T. (Box 30)
  - Haseltine, Orre B. (Box 30)
  - Hawk, Della J. (Box 30)
  - Hayes, Ruth I. (Box 30)
  - Heermans, Ruth (Box 30)
  - Helmer, Myra B. (Box 30)
  - Henckels, Marie I. (Box 30)
  - Henry, Ella M. (Box 30)
  - Hills, Leah S. (Box 30)
  - Hilton, Alice B. (Box 30)
  - Hincks, Sarah (Box 30)
  - Hobbs, Margarett A. (Box 30)
  - Hogg, Marion R. (Box 30)
  - Holloway, Lucie I. (Box 30)
  - Holme, Hilda P. (Box 30)
  - Howson, Marjorie (Box 30)
  - Hubbard, Helen P. (Box 30)
  - Huntington, Kate (Box 30)
  - Hyman, Hazel G. (Box 30)
  - Jamieson, Marguerite A. (Box 30)
  - Johnson, Louise H. (Box 30)
  - Johnson, Mabel L. (Box 30)
  - Jones, Margaret (Box 30)
  - Jones, Orpha E. (Box 30)
  - Kahler, Annette Marie (Box 30)
  - Keliher, Marguerite (Box 30)
  - Kellogg, Lois S. (Box 30)
  - Kennedy, Margaret (Box 30)
  - Kessler, Florence (Box 30)
  - Klein, Ella (Box 30)
  - Klenke, Anna L. (Box 30)
  - Klumph, Inez L. (Box 30)
  - Kurtz, Anna L. (Box 30)
  - Landon, Helen W. (Box 30)
  - Lansing, Elysabeth D. (Box 30)
  - LaRoche, Mary C. (Box 30)
  - Lauer, Edith M. (Box 30)
  - Lawson, Mabel E. (Box 30)
  - Lawton, Ruth W. (Box 30)
  - Leonard, Shirley (Box 30)
  - Leslie, Helen (Box 30)
  - Hornblower, Helen (Box 30)
  - Hosterman, Hazel D. (Box 30)
  - Hosterman, Helen H. (Box 30)
  - Houseman, Jessie L. (Box 30)
  - Howard, Edith E. (Box 30)
  - Lindner, Clara (Box 30)
  - Lobdell, Jessie K. (Box 30)
  - Loeb, Cecile (Box 30)
  - Loew, Bertha E. (Box 30)
  - Loomis, Sarah D. (Box 30)
  - Lovell, Gertrude (Box 30)
  - MacCullum, Mabel (Box 30)
  - Manatt, Evangeline I. (Box 30)
  - Manson, Katherine (Box 30)
  - Marceau, Ruth E. (Box 30)
  - Marcy, Irene R. (Box 30)
  - Mason, Ella L. (Box 30)
  - Mason, Marion C. (Box 30)
  - Maycock, Helen (Box 30)
  - McGuiness, Mary F. (Box 30)
  - McHugh, Adele L. (Box 30)
  - Meyers, Marion R. (Box 30)
  - Michaels, Mary B. (Box 30)
  - Miles, Irene L. (Box 30)
  - Milholland, Vida (Box 30)
  - Mills, Gertrude A. (Box 30)
  - Moores, Mary R. (Box 30)
  - Mosher, Gladys (Box 30)
  - Mumford, Anne M. (Box 30)
  - Murphy, Hazel Buckingham (Box 30)
  - Nash, Louise H. (Box 30)
  - Nelms, Emma Louise C. (Box 30)
  - Nilsen, Alma (Box 30)
  - Norris, Ethel L. (Box 30)
  - Norris, Margaret A. (Box 30)
  - Northe, Helen M. (Box 30)
  - Noyes, Fanny A. (Box 30)
  - Ockers, Louisa E. (Box 30)
  - O’Donnell, Kathleen G. (Box 31)
  - Orvis, Gertrude S. (Box 31)
  - Osborne, Eloise C. (Box 31)
  - Ostrander, Emma R. (Box 31)
  - Outterson, Frances M. (Box 31)
  - Palliser, Mabel B. (Box 31)
  - Pearl, Alice T. (Box 31)
  - Pelletier, Joanna O. (Box 31)
  - Plaut, Constance E. (Box 31)
  - Pennypacker, Julia E. (Box 31)
  - Powell, Margaret (Box 31)
  - Pratt, Hilda F. (Box 31)
  - Pratt, Marion (Box 31)
  - Pillsbury, Mary B. (Box 31)
  - Pierce, Elizabeth D. (Box 31)
  - Price, Marian (Box 31)
  - Prizer, Mary C. (Box 31)
  - Provost, E. Madeleine (Box 31)
  - Pulver, Mary I. (Box 31)
  - Rankin, Helen A. (Box 31)
  - Ransom, Caryl (Box 31)
  - Rauth, Lillian (Box 31)
  - Reckers, Louise F. (Box 31)
  - Reeb, Lauretta M. (Box 31)
  - Reed, Martha C. (Box 31)
  - Reed, Ruth A. (Box 31)
  - Rice, Beth C. (Box 31)
  - Rice, Elizabeth H. (Box 31)
  - Rice, Vera (Box 31)
  - Riker, Marion C. (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Mary Turlay (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Elizabeth T. (Box 31)
  - Rogers, Mary Barlow (Box 31)
  - Rundio, Helen (Box 31)
  - Rutherford, Elizabeth E. (Box 31)
  - Ryckman, Ruth E. (Box 31)
  - Sanger, Bettina L. (Box 31)
  - Sax, Clara R. (Box 31)
  - Scales, Ann M. (Box 31)
  - Schaefer, Geneva K. (Box 31)
  - Shelby, Florence M. (Box 31)
  - Sheldon, Elizabeth H. (Box 31)
  - Shelley, M. Margaret (Box 31)
  - Sherman, Estelle M. (Box 31)
  - Shoemaker, Helen R. (Box 31)
  - Sloan, Eleanor B. (Box 31)
  - Smart, Harriet S. (Box 31)
  - Smith, Annie C. (Box 31)
  - Smith, Dorothy (Box 31)
  - Smith, Emily D. (Box 31)
  - Smith, Helen E. (Box 31)
  - Smith, Juliet S. (Box 31)
  - Smith, Mary M. (Box 31)
  - Snyder, Helen C. (Box 31)
  - Somerville, Carol (Box 31)
  - Spear, Daisy H. (Box 31)
  - Spence, Alice G. (Box 31)
  - Spiegel, Katharine P. (Box 31)
  - Spies, Elisabeth (Box 31)
  - Starr, Ruth (Box 31)
  - Steams, Marianne (Box 31)
  - Steckel, Anna E. (Box 31)
  - Sterling, E. Corinda (Box 31)
  - Stiep, Jennie (Box 31)
  - Sillman, Dorothea (Box 31)
  - Stimson, Maude Beulah (Box 31)
  - Street, Mildred D. (Box 31)
  - Sullivan, Florence M. (Box 31)
  - Sweeney, E. Margery (Box 31)
  - Swiler, Elsie M. (Box 31)
  - Taft, Edith I. (Box 31)
  - Taylor, Katharine (Box 31)
  - Tichenor, Mabel E. (Box 31)
  - Tompkins, Helen W. (Box 31)
  - Topping, C. Beatrice (Box 31)
  - Traber, Bessie M. (Box 31)
  - Tucker, Marion E. (Box 31)
  - Tunnicliff, H. Dorothy (Box 31)
  - Turner, Marjorie S. (Box 31)
  - Tutt, Helen G. (Box 31)
  - Twiss, Alice G. (Box 31)
  - Underwood, Isabel (Box 31)
  - Underwood, Margaret C. (Box 31)
  - Urion, Frances Mary (Box 31)
  - Van Arsdale, Hester (Box 31)
  - Van Dyck, Katharine (Box 31)
  - Vaughn, Katharine E. (Box 31)
  - Vockrodt, Virginia J. (Box 31)
  - Vogel, Emilie S. (Box 31)
  - Wadhams, Florence D. (Box 31)
  - Wagner, Anne (Box 31)
  - Waldo, Mary R. (Box 31)
  - Wales, Marguerite A. (Box 31)
  - Warner, Margaret L. (Box 31)
  - Ware, Helen F. (Box 31)
  - Watts, Emma P. (Box 31)
  - Weed, Orlena (Box 31)
  - Weikert, Thekla E. (Box 31)
  - Whiley, Helen W. (Box 31)
  - Whitaker, Gertrude (Box 31)
  - White, Elizabeth F. (Box 31)
  - White, Gertrude M. (Box 31)
  - White, Helen D. (Box 31)
  - Whiting, E. Frances (Box 31)
  - Whitley, Elisabeth F. (Box 31)
  - Whysall, Ruth M. (Box 31)
  - Wightman, Susan W. (Box 31)
  - Willets, Martha (Box 31)
  - Williford, Ruth G. (Box 31)
  - Willis, Fifille (Box 31)
  - Wilson, Priscilla O. (Box 31)
  - Winters, Edna S. (Box 31)
  - Wolfersberger, Eda E. (Box 31)
  - Woodruff, Harriette S. (Box 31)
  - Woodruff, Wilda Eaton (Box 31)
  - Wyman, Edith H. (Box 31)
  - Young, Helen W. (Box 31)
  - Young, Phoebe Cordelia (Box 31)
  - Zohrlaut, Marguerite (Box 31)
  - Zimmerman, M. Louise (Box 31)
- Class of 1911
  - Adkins, Venice A. (Box 31)
  - Agerter, Rose E. (Box 31)
  - Altman, Madeleine (Box 31)
  - Andrews, Mary C. (Box 31)
  - Andrus, Elizabeth K. (Box 31)
  - Armstrong, Helen (Box 31)
  - Atherton, M. Valerie (Box 31)
  - Avery, Gladys M. (Box 31)
  - Babcock, Beatrice J. (Box 31)
  - Bacon, Carol S. (Box 31)
  - Balph, Helen R. (Box 31)
  - Bancroft, Jane (Box 31)
  - Barnet, Grace R. (Box 31)
  - Barr, Almeda (Box 31)
  - Bates, Beulah B. (Box 31)
  - Beach, Mary B. (Box 31)
  - Beebe, Ruth S. (Box 31)
  - Bell, Kathleen (Box 31)
  - Benedict, Agnes E.. (Box 31)
  - Bigelow, Ruth C. (Box 31)
  - Blood, Alma L. (Box 31)
  - Bond, Mildred M. (Box 31)
  - Bradley, Lucile (Box 31)
  - Bradley, Michael (Box 31)
  - Brady, Margaret L. (Box 31)
  - Breed, Mildred C. (Box 31)
  - Brewster, Helen E. (Box 31)
  - Breeze, Elizabeth L. (Box 31)
  - Brooks, Ada (Box 31)
  - Brown, Helen D. (Box 31)
  - Brown, Rose L. (Box 31)
  - Bulla, Beatrice (Box 31)
  - Bunn, Laura D. (Box 31)
  - Burnett, Charlotte C. (Box 31)
  - Butler, Virginia L. (Box 32)
  - Caldwell, Ruth H. (Box 32)
  - Calkins, Judith S. (Box 32)
  - Campbell, Elisabeth (Box 32)
  - Carl, Edna F. (Box 32)
  - Carroll, Godwin T. (Box 32)
  - Carter, Marjorie Dean (Box 32)
  - Carter, Mary E. (Box 32)
  - Cassidy, Florence G. (Box 32)
  - Chambers, Margaret (Box 32)
  - Chapin, Mary W. (Box 32)
  - Clark, Helen D. (Box 32)
  - Clark, Mabel (Box 32)
  - Clarke, Mary A. (Box 32)
  - Clements, Marjorie B. (Box 32)
  - Clinton, Caroline M. (Box 32)
  - Clouston, Edith R. (Box 32)
  - Collins, Edythe G. (Box 32)
  - Congdon, Helen C. (Box 32)
  - Conklin, Audrey (Box 32)
  - Connor, Harriet (Box 32)
  - Conway, Margaret S. (Box 32)
  - Conyne, Norma (Box 32)
  - Cracraft, Emma S. (Box 32)
  - Crampton, Marion E. (Box 32)
  - Crane, Mary Amelia (Box 32)
  - Crawford, Dorothy (Box 32)
  - Crawford, Wilda W. (Box 32)
  - Creegan, Helen C. (Box 32)
  - Crittenberger, Juliet V. (Box 32)
  - Curtis, Dorothea (Box 32)
  - Cutler, Mary Janet (Box 32)
  - Cutrer, Elise Jeannette (Box 32)
  - Danehower, Ruth (Box 32)
  - Davis, Florence Hume (Box 32)
  - Davis, Marguerite (Box 32)
  - DeLamater, Sarah L. (Box 32)
  - Dickerson, Eloise M. (Box 32)
  - Dinkey, Isabel E. (Box 32)
  - Dodge, Gertrude L. (Box 32)
  - Draper, Helen F. (Box 32)
  - Dumont, Ann G. (Box 32)
  - Dutcher, Winifred E. (Box 32)
  - Dyer, Mary B. (Box 32)
  - Eayrs, Ellen K. (Box 32)
  - Edgar, Margaret V. (Box 32)
  - Ellis, Pauline E. (Box 32)
  - Elwell, Florence R. (Box 32)
  - Emery, Helen C. (Box 32)
  - Estabrook, Louise W. (Box 32)
  - Fenton, Sagie V. (Box 32)
  - Ferguson, Margaret (Box 32)
  - Fiebeger, Julia F. (Box 32)
  - Fisher, Gladys (Box 32)
  - Fleetwood, Verna (Box 32)
  - Fletcher, G. Louise (Box 32)
  - Forbes, Katharine M. (Box 32)
  - Fowler, Mary (Box 32)
  - Frank, Grace D. (Box 32)
  - Fritz, M. Gladys (Box 32)
  - Gamage, Margaret E. (Box 32)
  - Gay, Dorothea (Box 32)
  - Geuder, Agnes F. (Box 32)
  - Gibson, Henrietta (Box 32)
  - Gnichtel, Julia S. (Box 32)
  - Goodrich, Constance (Box 32)
  - Graff, Jane (Box 32)
  - Graham, Elizabeth M. (Box 32)
  - Green, Marion M. (Box 32)
  - Greenhow, Olive M. (Box 32)
  - Hall, Caroline D. (Box 32)
  - Halsey, Ruth A. (Box 32)
  - Hamilton, Ruth C. (Box 32)
  - Hanford, Alice M. (Box 32)
  - Hanson, Helen T. (Box 32)
  - Harriman, M Frances (No file) (Box 32)
  - Hawley, Gertrude (Box 32)
  - Hays, Anne F. (Box 32)
  - Heath, Ruth H. (Box 32)
  - Heckel, Catherine P. (Box 32)
  - Heim, Myra M. (Box 32)
  - Heroy, Elizabeth (Box 32)
  - Herring, Laura D. (Box 32)
  - Hoard, Marjory (Box 32)
  - Hoff, Olga E. (Box 32)
  - Holloway, Marie Edna (Box 32)
  - Hopkins, Margarita S. (Box 32)
  - Hooker, Louise S. (Box 32)
  - Horn, Mildred L. (Box 32)
  - Horton, Elizabeth R. (Box 32)
  - Houghton, Helene S. (Box 32)
  - Hubbell, Elizabeth P. (Box 32)
  - Ingram, Cornelia M. (Box 32)
  - Jacobs, Lucile C. (Box 32)
  - Jeffcott, May E. (Box 32)
  - Jessup, Dorothy (Box 32)
  - Johnson, Abbie (Box 32)
  - Johnson, Mary G. (Box 32)
  - Judson, Claire deL (Box 32)
  - Kauffman, Elizabeth W. (Box 32)
  - Keffer, Bertha (Box 32)
  - Kelsey, Mabel E. (Box 32)
  - King, Marie M. (Box 32)
  - Knapp, J Isabel (Box 32)
  - Kneeland, Hildegarde (Box 32)
  - Kniffin, Marietta (Box 32)
  - Knight, Alice M. (Box 32)
  - Knowlton, Katherine A. (Box 32)
  - Knox, Mary L. (Box 32)
  - Krause, Hildegarde L. (Box 32)
  - Kretschmar, Constance (Box 32)
  - Kroener, Edna L. (Box 32)
  - Kudlich, Marjorie L. (Box 32)
  - Kuhl, Lora A. (Box 32)
  - Kurtz, Mabel Juliette (Box 32)
  - Kutzner, Anna W. (Box 32)
  - Kutzner, Elizabeth B. (Box 32)
  - Lacey, Florence (Box 32)
  - Lamprecht, Marjorie (Box 32)
  - Lane, Doris P. (Box 32)
  - Lathrop, Helen (Box 32)
  - Law, Helen H. (Box 32)
  - Leahy, Mary E. (Box 32)
  - Lecour, Eleanor L. (Box 32)
  - LeFevre, Gertrude M. (Box 32)
  - Lemon, Gertrude (Box 32)
  - Levi, Elsa B. (Box 32)
  - Lewis, Laura A. (Box 32)
  - Lewis, Sophia M. (Box 32)
  - Lovejoy, Julia S. (Box 32)
  - Loveland, Cara G. (Box 32)
  - Lowell, Gladys Mildred (Box 33)
  - Lynn, Joan (Box 33)
  - MacCoy, Marjorie N. (Box 33)
  - MacEnerney, Claire (Box 33)
  - MacNee, Ina (Box 33)
  - Manning, Katharine A. (Box 33)
  - Maxfield, Mary M. (Box 33)
  - Mayfield, Mary (Box 33)
  - McAusland, Mabel (Box 33)
  - McCarthy, Helen G. (Box 33)
  - McDavitt, Sarah C. (Box 33)
  - McLean, E Alberta (Box 33)
  - McNab, Christine S. (Box 33)
  - Menner, Dorothy H. (Box 33)
  - Mierendorff, Gertrude F. (Box 33)
  - Miller, Louise A. (Box 33)
  - Miller, Mabel M. (Box 33)
  - Miller, Mary I. (Box 33)
  - Miller, Maud E. (Box 33)
  - Mitchell, Ruth (Box 33)
  - Moon, Carolyn E. (Box 33)
  - Morey, Derexa W. (Box 33)
  - Moses, Ruth F. (Box 33)
  - Mossman, Helen H. (Box 33)
  - Mount, Helene F. (Box 33)
  - Mullen, Agnes G. (Box 33)
  - Munn, Margaret B. (Box 33)
  - Musser, Mary D. (Box 33)
  - Newton, Ruth C. (Box 33)
  - Noble, Mildred O. (Box 33)
  - Noyes, Helen R. (Box 33)
  - Noyes, Margaret S. (Box 33)
  - Nutting, Lois (Box 33)
  - Ogden, Elizabeth W. (Box 33)
  - Orr, Gertrude (Box 33)
  - Osborn, Frances (Box 33)
  - Owens, Beatrice (Box 33)
  - Paine, Helen V. (Box 33)
  - Palmer, Irene C. (Box 33)
  - Pattison, Jean H. (Box 33)
  - Patton, Marion L. (Box 33)
  - Pawling, Ethel E. (Box 33)
  - Peet, Marjorie (Box 33)
  - Perkins, Alice R. (Box 33)
  - Perkins, Dora (Box 33)
  - Perry, A Maida (Box 33)
  - Pierce, H Anne (Box 33)
  - Poppen, Sarah K. (Box 33)
  - Potter, Helen F. (Box 33)
  - Potter, Olga C. (Box 33)
  - Proudfoot, Helen (Box 33)
  - Purdy, Helen L. (Box 33)
  - Quarles, Ethel (Box 33)
  - Rea, Ethel Hague (Box 33)
  - Reed, Bonnie (Box 33)
  - Reynolds, Ethel M. (Box 33)
  - Rice, Dorothy L. (Box 33)
  - Rice, Edna R. (Box 33)
  - Rice, Fradelia (Box 33)
  - Rietow, Anna K. (Box 33)
  - Ritchie, Ellen A. (Box 33)
  - Robbins, Alpha (Box 33)
  - Robinson, Helen Avery (Box 33)
  - Rogers, Muriel W. (Box 33)
  - Rogers, Rosamund (Box 33)
  - Root, Iva M. (Box 33)
  - Rowe, Dorothy (Box 33)
  - Rude, Rachel (Box 33)
  - Schafer, Gertrude C. (Box 33)
  - Schaffer, Thusnelda (Box 33)
  - Schmidt, Elizabeth J (Box 33)
  - Schoenfield, Beatrice (Box 33)
  - Searle, Johannah S. (Box 33)
  - Shapleigh, Helen A. (Box 33)
  - Shaw, Geraldine (Box 33)
  - Shaw, Nettie (Box 33)
  - Sheldon, M Wanda (Box 33)
  - Shriver, Frances J (Box 33)
  - Simpson, Helen J (Box 33)
  - Sisson, M Louise (Box 33)
  - Smith, Effie B. (Box 33)
  - Smith, Elsie W. (Box 33)
  - Smith, Gertrude E. (Box 33)
  - Spann, Alice G. (Box 33)
  - Staples, Ruth L. (Box 33)
  - Starbuck, Kathryn H. (Box 33)
  - Stevens, Marion H. (Box 33)
  - Stiles, Agusta (Box 33)
  - Stockton, Elizabeth (Box 33)
  - Strasburg, Marjorie (Box 33)
  - Strachan, M Louise (Box 33)
  - Street, Grace H. (Box 33)
  - Strongman, Ruth (Box 33)
  - Sutphin, Dorothy H. (Box 33)
  - Sutton, Anna E. (Box 33)
  - Swan, Theo L. (Box 33)
  - Swift, Harriet (Box 33)
  - Tag, Florence K. (Box 33)
  - Tannewitz, Josephine (Box 33)
  - Terry, Jean (Box 33)
  - Thallon, Emily (Box 33)
  - Thorpe, Hazel (Box 33)
  - Tibbetts, Charlotte A. (Box 33)
  - Todd, Ruth W. (Box 33)
  - Tompkins, Beulah E. (Box 33)
  - Tompkins, Carolyn D. (Box 33)
  - Tonner, Adele E. (Box 33)
  - Trimble, Valpey C. (Box 33)
  - Tucker, Jessie Boughton (Box 33)
  - Tuttle, Elizabeth T. (Box 33)
  - Ulrich, Olive E. (Box 33)
  - Underhill, Alena O. (Box 33)
  - Van Harlingen, Edna (Box 33)
  - Van Zandt, Gladys M. (Box 33)
  - Vance, Emily (Box 33)
  - Vandegrift, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Vanston, Anne M. (Box 33)
  - Vine, Bessie (Box 33)
  - Vogt, Irene M. (Box 33)
  - Waite, Helen M. (Box 33)
  - Wallace, Lydia L. (Box 33)
  - Waller, Harriet A. (Box 33)
  - Walsh, Marion E. (Box 33)
  - Waterbury, Leah R. (Box 33)
  - Watson, Rebecca S. (Box 33)
  - Wean, Evangeline (Box 33)
  - Wellington, Beatrice (Box 33)
  - Wheeler, Lilias O. (Box 34)
  - Wheeler, Olive (Box 34)
  - Wheeler, Theodora (Box 34)
  - White, Dorothy (Box 34)
  - White, Marion H. (Box 34)
  - Wilcox, Stella (Box 34)
  - Williams, Genevieve J (Box 34)
  - Williams, May (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Elsie Louise (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Mary Lou (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Shirley E. (Box 34)
  - Wing, Alice T. (Box 34)
  - Winn, Mary D. (Box 34)
  - Wolcott, Hazel (Box 34)
  - Wolhaupter, Alice C. (Box 34)
  - Wright, Grace G. (Box 34)
  - Wright, Mary (Box 34)
  - Yates, L Katharine (Box 34)
  - Youngs, Martha E. (Box 34)
  - Zimmers, Lois (Box 34)
- Class of 1912
  - Abbot, Miriam (Box 34)
  - Ackerman, Florence E. (Box 34)
  - Adams, Katharine I. (Box 34)
  - Affleck, Grace Morris (Box 34)
  - Alden, Louise A. (Box 34)
  - Alden, Marie P. (Box 34)
  - Alexander, Lucy M. (Box 34)
  - Andrews, Esther C. (Box 34)
  - Arundell, Gladys F. (Box 34)
  - Atkins, Cornelia P. (Box 34)
  - Baker, Anne (Box 34)
  - Baldwin, Dorothy (Box 34)
  - Barber, Alice (Box 34)
  - Barnes, Mildred (Box 34)
  - Barney, Elizabeth (Box 34)
  - Barnitt, Ruth E. (Box 34)
  - Barrett, Florence (Box 34)
  - Baugh, Katharine L. (Box 34)
  - Benjamin, Ida E. (Box 34)
  - Benton, Helen G. (Box 34)
  - Berry, Margaret (Box 34)
  - Blackburn, Ruth H. (Box 34)
  - Blake, Anna H. (Box 34)
  - Blanding, Henriette deS (Box 34)
  - Blitz, Helen K. (Box 34)
  - Blount, Mamie E. (Box 34)
  - Bourne, Madeleine (Box 34)
  - Bouton, Katharine (Box 34)
  - Bowman, Helen (Box 34)
  - Boynton, Frieda F. (Box 34)
  - Brate, Charlotte (Box 34)
  - Brown, Edith C. (Box 34)
  - Brown, Hazel F. (Box 34)
  - Brown, Helen B. (Box 34)
  - Brown, Katharine M. (Box 34)
  - Browning, Mildred (Box 34)
  - Bruel, Anna L. (Box 34)
  - Bull, Clara S. (Box 34)
  - Burnham, Margaret (Box 34)
  - Burns, S Ruth (Box 34)
  - Burrowes, Alice K. (Box 34)
  - Butler, Laura A. (Box 34)
  - Butler, Margaret K. (Box 34)
  - Campbell, Cornelia H. (Box 34)
  - Carberry, Muriel (Box 34)
  - Carling, Elsie I. (Box 34)
  - Carpenter, Lela E. (Box 34)
  - Carroll, Courtney (Box 34)
  - Carver, Frances A. (Box 34)
  - Chaloner, Maud E. (Box 34)
  - Clarke, Louise C. (Box 34)
  - Clemence, Hazel (Box 34)
  - Clemens, Charlotte L. (Box 34)
  - Clevenger, Henrietta M. (Box 34)
  - Congdon, Caroline (Box 34)
  - Connell, Mary E. (Box 34)
  - Cowan, Frances M. (Box 34)
  - Cowen, Eleanor B. (Box 34)
  - Crawford, Ruth (Box 34)
  - Crossley, Marjorie W. (Box 34)
  - Cuddeback, Philenda A. (Box 34)
  - Culkin, Margaret F. (Box 34)
  - Cutler, Ruth (Box 34)
  - Cutter, Elizabeth (Box 34)
  - Davis, Belle (Box 34)
  - Davis, Emilie W. (Box 34)
  - De Schweinitz, Margaret (Box 34)
  - Deming, Dorothy F. (Box 34)
  - Denton, Edith M. (Box 34)
  - Dickerson, Ruth A. (Box 34)
  - Dickinson, Margaret (Box 34)
  - Dilman, Ethel E. (Box 34)
  - Douglass, Helen B. (Box 34)
  - Drumm, Marion S. (Box 34)
  - DuBois, Marguerite (Box 34)
  - Dudley, Edith S. (Box 34)
  - Dugan, Frances D. (Box 34)
  - Dunham, Marion G. (Box 34)
  - Dunlap, Dorothy J (Box 34)
  - Dyer, Elizabeth (Box 34)
  - Ecker, Ethel H. (Box 35)
  - Edge, Mary S. (Box 35)
  - Elliot, Gabrielle (Box 35)
  - English, Harriet H. (Box 35)
  - Ensley, Mary B. (Box 35)
  - Erwin, Eloise (Box 35)
  - Esten, Gladys L. (Box 35)
  - Everman, Marie T. (Box 35)
  - Faber, Dorothy E. (Box 35)
  - Farley, Jane (Box 35)
  - Farnam, Louise W. (Box 35)
  - Farrall, Bertrice A. (Box 35)
  - Fay, Dorothy W. (Box 35)
  - Fernald, Evelyn I. (Box 35)
  - Ferris, Helen J (Box 35)
  - Fitch, Ruth (Box 35)
  - Fisher, Mary G. (Box 35)
  - Fletcher, Mary (Box 35)
  - Flower, Mildred (Box 35)
  - Floyd, Marion B. (Box 35)
  - Foote, Sadie (Box 35)
  - Fowler, Kate G. (Box 35)
  - Freeland, Lucy S. (Box 35)
  - Fuller, Maud S. (Box 35)
  - Gale, Marguerite E. (Box 35)
  - Gallup, A Marie (Box 35)
  - Gardner, Katherine L. (Box 35)
  - Geary, Gertrude A. (Box 35)
  - Geary, Mary Elizabeth (Box 35)
  - Gleed, Dorothy C. (Box 35)
  - Goldman, Florence (Box 35)
  - Goodrich, Frances (Box 35)
  - Gowen, May C. (Box 35)
  - Green, Helen S. (Box 35)
  - Green, Ruth E. (Box 35)
  - Griff, Helen P. (Box 35)
  - Hackett, Grace M. (Box 35)
  - Hahlo, Gladys (Box 35)
  - Hale, Margaret (Box 35)
  - Hall, Helen C. (Box 35)
  - Hamilton, Ruth E. (Box 35)
  - Hand, Julia E. (Box 35)
  - Harris, Marjorie M. (Box 35)
  - Hartmann, Bertha I. (Box 35)
  - Hartmann, Charlotte E. (Box 35)
  - Henry, Jane F. (Box 35)
  - Herold, Verna (Box 35)
  - Herrick, Martha P. (Box 35)
  - Hert, Lilian F. (Box 35)
  - Heywood, Helen (Box 35)
  - Hodgman, Gertrude E. (Box 35)
  - Hogg, Mildred E. (Box 35)
  - Hooker, Carolyn (Box 35)
  - Hooker, M Alice (Box 35)
  - Hoornbeek, Ethel B. (Box 35)
  - Hornickel, Edith (Box 35)
  - Hurlbutt, Mary E. (Box 35)
  - Hull, Ethel M. (Box 35)
  - Hutchinson, E Lillian (Box 35)
  - Ives, Marian F. (Box 35)
  - Jackson, Helen (Box 35)
  - James, Helen C. (Box 35)
  - James, Ruth F. (Box 35)
  - Jennings, Margaret (Box 35)
  - Johnson, Frances (Box 35)
  - Johnston, Ruth B. (Box 35)
  - Keeney, Charlotte F. (Box 35)
  - Keniston, Ethel D. (Box 35)
  - Kennedy, Eliza J (Box 35)
  - Kilgen, Viola A. (Box 35)
  - Kittredge, Elizabeth (Box 35)
  - Knowlton, Sylvia P. (Box 35)
  - Koerner, Grace E. (Box 35)
  - Lancaster, Olive H. (Box 35)
  - Large, Helen B. (Box 35)
  - Latham, Alberta N. (Box 35)
  - Lawrence, Irene (Box 35)
  - Lemon, E Corinne (Box 35)
  - Lesher, M Alice (Box 35)
  - Leslie, Alma V. (Box 35)
  - Lewis, Mary S. (Box 35)
  - Linsley, Irene P. (Box 35)
  - Lockwood, Helen D. (Box 35)
  - Loosen, Loraine (Box 35)
  - Lovell, Lucy C. (Box 35)
  - Lutz, Alma (Box 36)
  - Maas, Edith H. (Box 36)
  - MacNaughton, Mary E. (Box 36)
  - Magnuson, Ruth V. (Box 36)
  - McCarthy, Caroline H. (Box 36)
  - McCay, Mary E. (Box 36)
  - McClave, Maude M. (Box 36)
  - McCullough, Ethel (Box 36)
  - McGregor, Kate I. (Box 36)
  - McKee, Dorothy (Box 36)
  - McWilliams, Helen I. (Box 36)
  - Mead, Mary E. (Box 36)
  - Merritt, Eleanor H. (Box 36)
  - Miller, Gladys E. (Box 36)
  - Miller, Mary B. (Box 36)
  - Mitchell, Katharine (Box 36)
  - Moore, Agnes D. (Box 36)
  - Moore, Susan (Box 36)
  - Morehouse, Reba E. (Box 36)
  - Mount, M Marie (Box 36)
  - Murray, Isabelle L. (Box 36)
  - Myers, Louisa B. (Box 36)
  - Naumberg, Margaret (Box 36)
  - Nightingale, Nina (Box 36)
  - Olds, Florence (Box 36)
  - Otis, Katherine E. (Box 36)
  - Page, Elizabeth M. (Box 36)
  - Pearce, A Josephine (Box 36)
  - Peepels, Marguerite E. (Box 36)
  - Peters, Margaret (Box 36)
  - Pidgeon, Marie K. (Box 36)